question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "'Half-Life 2' runs on the Source Engine.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In 'Space Station 13',  the station has a clown aboard it.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Terraria, you can craft the Cell Phone pre-hardmode.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Solid Snake is actually a clone from the DNA of Big Boss in the Metal Gear Solid series history.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Team Fortress 2, being disguised as a scout or medic results in a speed boost.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Big the Cat is a playable character in 'Sonic Generations'.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Each piece in Tetris is called a tetris.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Kingdom Hearts the Paopu fruit is said to intertwine the destinies for two people forever.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Tetris is the #1 best-selling video game of all-time.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The name of the main character of the video game 'The Legend of Zelda', is Zelda.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The game 'Jetpack Joyride' was created by 'Redbrick Studios'.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The ultimate phrase used by Pharah from Overwatch is: 'Justice rains from above!'",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
